Forecast Fragment类中
In the Forecast Fragment class,
我们添加了回调接口，它提供了一个依据
we add the Callback interface
that was provided in the gist.
然后在onCreateView函数里改变列表项点击事件
Then, in the onCreateView method,
we modify the list item click behavior.
当列表项被点击，不同于总是加载一个新的intent来启动
When an item is clicked, instead of
always launching a new intent to
detail activity，我们希望通知回调接口
the detail activity,
we want to notify the Callback instead.
调用getActivity方法
We call getActivity and
强转成一个Callback对象，这样我们可以调用onItemSelected
then cast it to a Callback object,
then we can call onItemSelected on it.
我们传递这个描述位置信息数据的URI
We pass the URI that represents
the selected location and date.
然后在main_activity里实现这个回调接口
Then, in the main activity,
we implement the Callback interface.
在onItemSelected函数里，根据之前定义的mTwoPane变量
In the onItemSelected method, we fork
the behavior based on the mTwoPane
来分支这个行为
variable that we defined earlier.
如果我们在两个窗格模式下，就创建一个DetailFragment
If we're in two-pane mode,
then we create a DetailFragment and
把URI数据放进arguments bundle
put the URI inside the arguments bundle.
然后在weather_detail_container中，使用DETAILFRAGMENT_TAG
Then we replace the existing
DetailFragment in
替换掉现在的DetailFragment
the weather_detail_container,
using the DETAILFRAGMENT_TAG.
在单窗格模式，我们创建一个新的intent加载DetailActivity
In one pane mode, we create a new
Intent to launch the DetailActivity and
设置数据URI
we set the data URI.
在DetailActivity里
In the DetailActivity,
改变onCreate来从进来的intent里读取数据URI
we modify the onCreate method to read
the data URI from the incoming intent.
我们使用这个URI，设置它为新的DetailFragment的属性
We take the URI and set it as
an arguments in the new DetailFragment.
然后动态的添加fragment到容器中
Then we dynamically add this
fragment to this container.
在detai_fragment里，我们改变onCreateView函数让它
In the detail fragment,
we modify the onCreateView method
读取初始化这个fragment所使用的arguments
to read the arguments that
the fragment was initialized with.
我们读取数据URI并且存储在成员变量mUri
We read the data URI and
store that in the member variable mUri.
在OnCreateLoader函数里，我们移除掉一些依赖传入的intent的代码
In the OnCreateLoader method,
we remove some code that relied on
并选择用mUri代替
incoming intent, and
switched it to use mUri instead.
不管DetailFragment是在main_activity还是在DetailActivity
Whether this DetailFragment is in
the main activity or the DetailActivity,
它都有mUri的设置
it should have mUri set.
接下来我们将使用mUri来查询内容提供者的数据
Then we're going to use mUri to
query the content provider for
来显示在DetailFragment上
the data to display in
this DetailFragment.
当你在平板上测试的时候
When you try it out on the tablet,
有一个和导航栏有关的bug需要解决
there is one bug related to
navigation that we should fix.
我们选择明天的数据，如果你导航到settings activity
Say we select tomorrow's date, if you
navigate to the settings activity, and
然后点击向上的按键，detail fragment变空了
then hit the up button,
the detail fragment is blank.
这是因为新的main activity的实例被加载了
That's because a brand new instance
of main activity got launched, and
默认是没有选择任何数据的
for a brand new instance,
nothing is selected yet.
为了解决这个bug,当settings activity向上按键被按下的时候
To fix this, when the setting activity
up button is pressed, we want to
我们希望导航到前一个运行的main activity实例
navigate to the previous running
instance of the main activity where
并且明天的选项依然被选中，但现在它创建了一个新的实例
the tomorrow item is selected and now
create a new instance of main activity.
在SettingsActivity里重写这个方法
In the SettingsActivity, override this
method, which the system will call
系统将会调用它来得到父activity的intent来处理向上按键的事件
in order to get the parent activity
intent for the up button behavior.
在父类里得到父activity
Get the parent activity
intent from the super class,
这将创建一个新的main_activity
this should create a new
intent to main activity.
然后添加intent_flag，名字是FLAG_ACTIVITY_CLEAR_TOP
Then add the intent flag called
FLAG_ACTIVITY_CLEAR_TOP.
这个flag的意思是，我们应该检查是否在task中存在
This flag indicates that we should
check if the main activity is
已经运行的 main activity
already running in our task.
并且使用它代替创建一个新的实例
And to use that one instead of
creating a new main activity instance.
这个方法在Jelly bean之前的版本中不存在
Also this method didn't
exist prior to Jelly Bean so
我们需要添加@TargetApi 注解
we need to add this
@TargetApi annotation.
如果你查阅activity的文档
If you check the documentation for
the activity class,
getParentActivityIntent方法只能在高于api 16的版本使用
the getParentActivityIntent method
was only added in API level 16,
你可以查到api 16 对应的版本是Jelly Bean
and you can check that version
16 maps to Jelly Bean.